Ed Ho

• Connecticut, United States

**** 8608779728

in linkedin.com/in/imedho

■ edhodesign@gmail.com

k imedho.github.io

instagram.com/imedho



■ Profile

I am a designer that specializes in paper engineering. I have been working with paper my whole life and am an expert when it comes to anything made out of paper such as: business cards, envelopes, specialized advertisements, pop up cards, and packaging.

Professional Experience

Professional Experience		
06/2018 – 08/2018	Animax Designs, Assembly Intern Assembled various amusement park animatronics and solved design problems.	Nashville, Tennessee
09/2016 – 11/2016	Ballard Institute and Museum of Puppetry, Museum Assistant Set up museum displays and guest speaker live streams.	Storrs, Connecticut
 Education		

University of Connecticut, Graphic Design Storrs, USA 2016 - 2020

🕅 Skills

- Paper Engineering
- Graphic Design
- Motion Graphics
- 3D Modeling | Rhino, Fusion 360, Blender
- Structural Packaging Design
- Video Production
- Adobe | Illustrator, After Effects, Photoshop, InDesign
- AutoCAD